[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "1. What prompted the conversation?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. The man wants to place a classified ad in the newspaper."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. The woman wants to find an apartment close to school."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. The man wants to pay for a newspaper subscription."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. The woman wants to fill out an application for employment."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "2. What does the man want to sell?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. Furniture."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. Books."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. Garden supplies."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. An apartment."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "3. What is the man's last name?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. Martin."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. Martyn."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. Wynn."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. Wartin."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "B"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "4. How will the man pay?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. He will pay by check."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. He will have the amount billed to his home address."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. He will come back to pay when he is billed."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. He will give the woman cash."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "D"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "5. Why does the man decide to revise what he has written?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. To make it clearer to understand."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. To make it longer to read."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. To make it cheaper to print."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. To make it easies to use."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "1. What is the purpose of the conversation?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. To help the woman make a purchase."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. To request the woman's identification."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. To show the woman how to make out a check."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. To register the woman for a course at City College."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "2. What is meant by the term cash?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. Money."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. Money or credit cards."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. Credit cards or checks."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. Checks or money."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "D"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "3. How does the woman pay for her purchase?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. Credit cards."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. Money."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. Debit card."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. check."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "D"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "4. What did the woman use as identification?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. She used her student ID card and a charge card."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. She used her credit card."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. She used her driver's license and her student ID card."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. She used her telephone number and her student ID card."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "5. Who is the man in this conversation?",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. A clerk."
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. The woman's husband."
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. A police officer."
			},
			{
				"value": "D",
				"text": "D. A bank teller."
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	}
]